{
    "subject": "resource/Gustav_Rydahl",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Gustav Rydahl was born in Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9561746120452881,
            "question": "If Gustav Rydahl was born in Sweden, what cultural influences might he have experienced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9393871426582336,
            "question": "Is Gustav Rydahl Swedish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9046884775161743,
            "question": "Where was Gustav Rydahl born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7221860289573669,
            "question": "What country is associated with Gustav Rydahl's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5477148294448853,
            "question": "What can we infer about Gustav Rydahl's nationality based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041686296463013,
            "question": "How might Gustav Rydahl's birthplace have shaped his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4356752634048462,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything about Gustav Rydahl's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3514132797718048,
            "question": "Where might Gustav Rydahl have spent his early years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29028743505477905,
            "question": "What are some characteristics often associated with people born in Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20345665514469147,
            "question": "Do you know any other notable individuals from Sweden?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gustav Rydahl was born in Sweden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4805_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some characteristics often associated with people born in Sweden?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4805_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Gustav Rydahl have spent his early years?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4805_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me anything about Gustav Rydahl's origins?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4805_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4805_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it contains details about a person named Gustav Rydahl. However, his date of birth is mentioned as September 11, 1994 (in document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4805/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt), not May 31, 1987 (as mentioned in the query). Therefore, the information in the documents does not support the statement that Gustav Rydahl was born on May 31, 1987.\n\nThe response should be:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Gustav Rydahl was born on September 11, 1994, in Karlstad, Sweden. This supports the statement that Gustav Rydahl was born in Sweden."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The birthdate of Gustav Rydahl was stated as September 11, 1994, on the first piece of information.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}